Browning W. Ware papers, Inclusive: 1928-2002, undated, Bulk: 1954-1988
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Personal Materials, 1949-2000, undated; 3
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (1 of 9), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (2 of 9), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (3 of 9), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (4 of 9), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (5 of 9), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (6 of 9), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (7 of 9), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (8 of 9), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (9 of 9), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Take Five (1 of 4), 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Take Five (2 of 4), 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Take Five (3 of 4), 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Take Five (4 of 4), 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to and from Hibbert (1 of 3), 1983-1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to and from Hibbert (2 of 3), 1983-1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to and from Hibbert (3 of 3), 1983-1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1983-1995 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1983-1995 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1983-1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1983-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1983-1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Manual Brent (1 of 4), 1986-1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Manual Brent (2 of 4), 1986-1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Manual Brent (3 of 4), 1986-1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Manual Brent (4 of 4), 1986-1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - High School class paper, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Thesis by James Dunn, “A Christian Encounter with Contemporary Collectivism”, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Thesis by William Estep Jr., “A Survey of the Distinctive Ethical Emphases at Various Periods”, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Organizational Memberships, 1981-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Various Speeches (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Various Speeches (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Clayton Brokerage Company, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Will, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - General Photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - General Photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Retirement Photographs (1 of 5), circa 1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Retirement Photographs (2 of 5), circa 1996 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Retirement Photographs (3 of 5), circa 1996 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Retirement Photographs (4 of 5), circa 1996 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Retirement Photographs (5 of 5), circa 1996 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- University Studies, 1951-1984, undated; 4
  This series contains materials from Ware's studies at Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary, and other universities. Also included are documents from when Ware studied at Harvard later in life.
  - “A Brief History of the Discipline of Old Testament Theology”, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - “Aristotle: His Life and Some Chief Thought”, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - “Philosophy of Wilhelm Dilthey”, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - “Alan Richardson: Christian Apologist”, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - “The Ephesian Mission”, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - “Introduction to Spiritual Life” class (1 of 3), undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - “Introduction to Spiritual Life” class (2 of 3), undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - “Introduction to Spiritual Life” class (3 of 3), undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Old Testament Theology Term Papers (1 of 2), 1956 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Old Testament Theology Term Papers (2 of 2), 1956 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Partial Term Paper (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Partial Term Paper (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Ethics Class Papers (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ethics Class Papers (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Christian Ethics taught by Dr. T.B. Maston (1 of 3), 1956 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Christian Ethics taught by Dr. T.B. Maston (2 of 3), 1956 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Christian Ethics taught by Dr. T.B. Maston (3 of 3), 1956 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Christian Ethics Class (1 of 2), 1959 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Christian Ethics Class (2 of 2), 1959 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Philosophy Class, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Ethics Class, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Spring 1955 Syllabi (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Spring 1955 Syllabi (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Church History class, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Christian Ethics class (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Christian Ethics class (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Philosophy of Religion class (1 of 3), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Philosophy of Religion class (2 of 3), 1955 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Philosophy of Religion class (3 of 3), 1955 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Ethics class (1 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ethics class (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Greek New Testament class, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Ethics Class notes, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - History Class Notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Greek Class Notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Class Notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Harvard classes (1 of 7), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Harvard classes (2 of 7), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Harvard classes (3 of 7), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Harvard classes (4 of 7), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Harvard classes (5 of 7), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Harvard classes (6 of 7), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Harvard classes (7 of 7), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Harvard Notes, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Preparation for Orals, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Class Notes and Letters (1 of 8), circa 1950 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Class Notes and Letters (2 of 8), circa 1950 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Class Notes and Letters (3 of 8), circa 1950 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Class Notes and Letters (4 of 8), circa 1950 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Class Notes and Letters (5 of 8), circa 1950 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Class Notes and Letters (6 of 8), circa 1950 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Class Notes and Letters (7 of 8), circa 1950 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Class Notes and Letters (8 of 8), circa 1950 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Sermons, 1951-1995, undated; 5
  This series contains sermons authored by Dr. Browning Ware, through the different churches he served and the various revivals and other speaking engagements he did that required sermons. Also included are inspirational stories and notes that Ware drew content or inspiration from for his sermons, and some sermons not by Browning Ware that nevertheless influenced his sermons.
  - Sermon Log, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (1 of 2), 1957-1959 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (2 of 2), 1957-1959 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (1 of 2), circa 1965 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Sermons (2 of 2), circa 1965 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Sermons, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Sermons, Notes (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Sermons, Notes (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Sermons (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Sermons, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (1 of 6), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (2 of 6), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (3 of 6), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (4 of 6), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (5 of 6), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (6 of 6), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Sermons (1 of 6), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Sermons (2 of 6), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Sermons (3 of 6), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (4 of 6), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (5 of 6), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Sermons (6 of 6), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (1 of 5), 1975 March (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (2 of 5), 1975 March (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (3 of 5), 1975 March (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (4 of 5), 1975 March (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (5 of 5), 1975 March (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Sermons, Gold Label Preaching-Ed Crow, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (1 of 5), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (2 of 5), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (3 of 5), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Sermons (1 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (2 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (3 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Sermons (4 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (5 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (6 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (7 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (8 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (9 of 9), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (1 of 5), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (2 of 5), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (3 of 5), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (4 of 5), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (5 of 5), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (1 of 5), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (2 of 5), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (3 of 5), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (4 of 5), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Sermons, Transcribed (5 of 5), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Sermons (1 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (2 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (3 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (4 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (5 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (6 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (7 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (8 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (9 of 9), 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Sermons, Other, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Sermons, Notes (1 of 4), 1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Sermons, Notes (2 of 4), 1978 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Sermons, Notes (3 of 4), 1978 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Sermons, Notes (4 of 4), 1978 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Sermons, Typed, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Sermons, Notes (1 of 4), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Sermons, Notes (2 of 4), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Sermons, Notes (3 of 4), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Sermons, Notes (4 of 4), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Sermons (1 of 2), circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Sermons (2 of 2), circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Sermons (1 of 4), 1980 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Sermons (2 of 4), 1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (3 of 4), 1980 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (4 of 4), 1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Sermons: Guest Speaker, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (4 of 4), 1981 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Sermons: "Communion Meditation", 1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (1 of 4), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (2 of 4), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (3 of 4), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Sermons (4 of 4), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Sermons: "Theology of Woundedness", 1983 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Sermons, Notes (1 of 5), 1983 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Sermons, Notes (2 of 5), 1983 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Sermons, Notes (3 of 5), 1983 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Sermons, Notes (4 of 5), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Sermons, Notes (5 of 5), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Sermons (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Sermons: "Christian Citizens", 1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (1 of 5), 1984 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (2 of 5), 1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (3 of 5), 1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (4 of 5), 1984 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (5 of 5), 1984 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Sermons (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Sermons, Notes (1 of 4), 1985 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Sermons, Notes (2 of 4), 1985 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Sermons, Notes (3 of 4), 1985 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Sermons, Notes (4 of 4), 1985 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (1 of 4), 1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Sermons (2 of 4), 1986 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (3 of 4), 1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (4 of 4), 1986 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Sermons, Cliff Temple Revival, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (1 of 5), 1987 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (2 of 5), 1987 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (3 of 5), 1987 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (4 of 5), 1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (5 of 5), 1987 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Sermons (1 of 5), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Sermons (2 of 5), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Sermons (3 of 5), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Sermons (4 of 5), 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (5 of 5), 1988 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (1 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Sermons (2 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (3 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (4 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (5 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (6 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (7 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (8 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (9 of 9), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (1 of 4), 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Sermons (2 of 4), 1990 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Sermons (3 of 4), 1990 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Sermons (4 of 4), 1990 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Sermons (1 of 6), 1991 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Sermons (2 of 6), 1991 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Sermons (3 of 6), 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (4 of 6), 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (5 of 6), 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Sermons (6 of 6), 1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (1 of 6), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (2 of 6), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (3 of 6), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (4 of 6), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (5 of 6), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (6 of 6), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Sermons (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Sermons (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Sermons (1 of 3), 1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Sermons (2 of 3), 1994 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Sermons (3 of 3), 1994 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Sermons, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Sermons, 1995 October-December (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (1 of 4), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (2 of 4), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (3 of 4), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Sermons, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (1 of 2), 1962-1976 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (2 of 2), 1962-1976 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Kathwood Baptist Church (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Kathwood Baptist Church (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Sermons Preached in Hubbard, Texas (1 of 2), undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Sermons Preached in Hubbard, Texas (2 of 2), undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Sermons (1 of 4), undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Sermons (2 of 4), undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Sermons (3 of 4), undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Sermons (4 of 4), undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Sermons (1 of 3), undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Sermons (2 of 3), undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (3 of 3), undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Church Bulletins, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Sermon Notes (1 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Sermon Notes (2 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Sermon Notes (3 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Sermon Notes (4 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Sermon Notes (5 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Sermon Notes (6 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Sermon Notes (7 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Sermon Notes (8 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Sermon Notes (9 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Sermon Notes (10 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Sermon Notes (11 of 11), circa 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sermon Notes (1 of 2), undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Sermon Notes (2 of 2), undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Inspirational Items (1 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Inspirational Items (2 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - “Revivals in the Bible” by E.D. Head, thesis, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - “Carlyle Marney: Pilgrim-Prophet” by Shurden and Tupper, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - “The Stream of Life” by Hal Potts, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - "Temptations of Jesus" sermon by Marney, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Sermons not by Browning Ware, 1957-1965 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Sermons not by Browning Ware (1 of 3), 1958-1964 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Sermons not by Browning Ware (2 of 3), 1958-1964 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Sermons not by Browning Ware (3 of 3), 1958-1964 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Audio Recordings, 1957-1962, undated; 6
  This series contains a specialized kind of LP record produced using a Gray Audograph machine, and audio cassette tapes. Recorded on this media are Browning Ware's sermons for select years. Many of these sermons, but not all of them, have been transcribed.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Cassette tape; Phonodisc
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (1 of 8), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (2 of 8), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (3 of 8), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (4 of 8), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (5 of 8), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (6 of 8), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (7 of 8), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (8 of 8), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (1 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (2 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (3 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (4 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (5 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (6 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (7 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (8 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (9 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (10 of 10), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (1 of 7), 1959 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (2 of 7), 1959 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (3 of 7), 1959 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (4 of 7), 1959 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (5 of 7), 1959 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (6 of 7), 1959 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (7 of 7), 1959 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (1 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (2 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (3 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (4 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (5 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (6 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (7 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (8 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (9 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (10 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (11 of 11), 1960 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (1 of 8), undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (2 of 8), undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (3 of 8), undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (4 of 8), undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (5 of 8), undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (6 of 8), undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (7 of 8), undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Gray Audograph Phonodisk Recordings (8 of 8), undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1975 February 23-1975 September 21 (Box 43 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1975 September 28-1976 April 4 (Box 44 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1976 April 11-1976 August 1 (Box 45 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1976 August 22-1977 February (Box 46 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1977 February 13-1977 July 10 (Box 47 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1977 July 17-1977 December 25 (Box 48 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1978 January 1-1978 June 18 (Box 49 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1978 June 25-1978 October 15 (Box 50 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1978 October 22-1979 March 24 (Box 51 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1979 March 25-1979 September 9 (Box 52 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1979 September 16-1980 March 2 (Box 53 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1980 March 9-1980 July 27 (Box 54 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1980 August 3-1980 December 14 (Box 55 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1980 December 21-1981 May 31 (Box 56 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1981 May 31-1981 November 8 (Box 57 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1981 November 15-1982 April 11 (Box 58 OVZ)